If I had to describe him...
He was like the sun.
His dazzling warmth and attitude
put a smile on everyone's faces.
I was sure our paths would never cross.
At least, that's what I'd assumed.
Does that mean you like me, Suzuki?
Hey.
Don't shy away.
Give me an answer.
How did I get here?
Am I dreaming?
Or is this...
[Episode 1]
[WIP]
[6:30 AM - Alarm]
Crap.
Hajime Suzuki, high school sophomore.
I like to write stories and daydream.
[Stars in the Deep Sea]
My genre of choice is BL.
In short, I'm a "fudanshi".
[T/N: Guy who likes BL (Boys Love)]
But I only enjoy consuming BL.
I haven't ever fallen for a real guy.
If anything,
romance isn't really for a guy like me.
Girls treat me like thin air anyway.
Hey, um...
- It's mine now.
- Gimme.
What? No!
- Can I...
- Nuh-uh.
You're not having it.
Never!
Long story short,
I've given up on relationships.
Did you finish the assignment?
- Shoot, I forgot.
- Let's cram together.
- What?
- Come on, please?
- No thanks.
- I'm begging you.
I don't even have a friend.
I'm a complete loner.
My renowned classmates on the other hand,
are my complete opposite.
- Morning.
- Hey guys!
- 'Sup?
Yuma Saeki.
A good-looking, sociable fashionista.
[Yuma Saeki - 32,000 Followers]
- Morning, Koha.
- Morning.
Your makeup looks different today.
Oh, yeah. Does it look weird?
Nope. You look as cute as ever.
Shut up!
All right, enough flirting you two.
Our resident meathead is jealous.
Hey, I'm no meathead.
I'm a "muscle"-head.
- Same difference.
- Yeah.
As if. See? Muscles, not meat.
Shun Iwasaki.
A member of our judo team.
Known for his strength and physique.
But he was at a disadvantage! That's crazy...
- Score!
- He's the best in the prefecture.
I bet he'll be recruited
for the national team.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Iwasaki.
Did you do the math worksheet due today?
Shoot, I forgot.
Takeuchi.
Let me copy yours.
Not happening. Do it yourself.
Tomoaki Takeuchi.
A chill guy, known for his smarts.
Holy cow, he got straight A's!
Takeuchi always scores top ten
on the national mock exams.
How? I don't ever see him study.
He must be a genius.
All right everyone, settle down.
Hey, where's Serizawa?
Beats me.
Probably late again.
And the last member of their posse...
What's up, class?
Haruto Serizawa.
Tone it down, Serizawa.
You're not even on time.
I'm practically on time.
Which means you're late.
For real?
- Cut me some slack, Mr. Usami.
- Not happening.
Aw, pretty please?
You're not changing my mind, kid.
Now get to your seat.
Yes, sir.
These four good-looking dudes,
are the most popular guys in our school.
Score!
When my sophomore year began,
I became classmates with Serizawa.
He quickly had me enthralled.
He's as cool as ever.
Because in my eyes,
Serizawa was the perfect top.
[Haruto Serizawa]
And so,
I began writing a BL novel
with Serizawa as the main character.
It's definitely over here.
You sure? You were wrong yesterday.
If anyone found out about my little hobby...
Let's get outta here.
Yeah. Anyone up for karaoke?
Where is it?
You looking for something, Suzuki?
S-Seri...
Serizawa?
Um, I...
Let me guess.
Looking for this?
Wh-Why... H-How...
You were sitting where I found it,
so I assumed.
Here.
Makes sense.
Th-Thank you.
Huh?
You write about a "Haruto Serizawa" in here.
Is that supposed to be me?
It's so over.
Suzuki?
Hello? Anyone home?
I... I...
I'm so sorry!
Huh? Hey, your notebook!
I ended up running away.
What do I do? Serizawa's definitely mad.
Actually,
there's a bigger problem...
[Year 1, Class 3]
Did you hear what Suzuki reads?
- Yeah.
- I can't believe it.
It sort of grosses me out.
Same.
Why would a guy like BL?
- Beats me.
- Maybe he's eyeing you.
- Dude, not funny.
- You sure?
- Don't be shy.
- You two are the perfect pair!
- Stop that, seriously.
- Aw, you'll break his heart.
Apologize first.
Then, get my notebook back.
All right, you can do this.
You can do this.
Okay.
Damn...
- One more round!
- You're on.
There!
Go, go!
I can't do this! I can't!
It's impossible!
Lunch showdown in three,
two, one...
That's a strong contender.
Those four practically sparkle.
I could never call out to them.
Store-bought isn't homemade. Disqualified.
It's made somewhere!
It's not the same.
See? Look at my beautiful lunch.
Not bad.
It's cute.
All right, let's start with warm-ups.
Find a partner and get stretching.
Whoever's left, come to me.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
Sit down.
Come on, Serizawa.
Sorry, not today.
Suzuki.
Let's get stretching.
- Huh?
- Are even you trying?
You're as stiff as a board.
- You can go farther.
- Ow!
Breath out, and hold.
I don't understand.
Why is Serizawa stretching with me?
He has to be mad about yesterday...
Takeuchi? Why're you paired with Usami?
Serizawa dumped me.
Aw...
Poor you!
Hey! It's not so bad working out with me.
Whatever you say.
Right, Takeuchi?
I guess.
See?
Has Serizawa even spoken to Suzuki before?
Focus on your own stretches.
I feel like everyone's staring at us.
And is it just me, or...
Is he really close?
You okay?
Are you feeling sick?
I'm fine.
But your ears.
They're turning red.
Get me out of here!
Mr. Usami, can I take Suzuki to the nurse?
He's looking sick.
Huh?
Sure. Take it easy, Suzuki.
N-No, I'm...
Here, hop on.
But...
Don't keep me hanging.
Serizawa...
Sorry.
- I'm not actually sick.
- Yeah.
I know.
Huh?
Then where are we going?
Somewhere we can be alone.
The classroom?
Your stop, sir.
Thanks.
I could tell you wanted to talk.
So, I figured it'd be easier if we were alone.
Here.
T-Thanks.
So...
[Idea Journal]
About this notebook...
Do you write BL?
Yeah.
Since you're basing a character off me,
does that mean...
You like me, Suzuki?
Hey, don't shy away.
Give me an answer.
I, uh...
I...
I'm so sorry!
Huh? Wait, I'm confused.
I used your likeness without your permission,
and caused a major misunderstanding.
I'm so terribly sorry!
Suzuki, look at me.
I just enjoy BL works.
I even think you're the ideal top.
But my romantic orientation
has nothing to do with my BL hobby.
So, I never looked at you in that way.
I see.
I'm sorry I made you feel uncomfortable.
I'll try to make it up to you.
How?
I can pay for the damage done?
Actually, I'm too broke for that...
But I promise I'll do whatever I can.
Really? Anything?
Yeah.
So...
I mean...
Please don't tell anyone else about this.
All right, deal.
Then how's this?
Let me read it.
That novel of yours.
Huh?
I should clear something up.
I'm not mad at you.
If anything, I'm honored.
Huh?
I also think I'm a top.
What?
Right, sorry.
I'm actually a BL fan, too.
You are?
Is it that surprising?
Yeah.
Why? Anyone can read BL, right?
So, what sort of stuff do you read?
I like Tatakiwari Ishibashi's works.
I like their works, too.
Seriously? A fellow fan with great taste!
Give me five!
Five.
Now I really want to read your novel.
Well...
You said you'd do anything.
But my writing isn't good.
And it's not done.
Not to mention no one else
has read it before...
Then I guess I get to be your very first.
Huh?
Come on, please?
Give me the honor
of being your first reader.
That's a good line.
Oh, did that one get to you?
Yeah.
But how about this instead?
"Suzuki, give me all your very firsts".
That's a good one!
Let me give it another go.
Suzuki.
Give me all your very firsts.
How was that?
Suzuki?
Hello?
You okay?
That...
Was...
Amazing.
You scared me for a second there.
So, how about it?
Will you give me the honor
of being your first?
Yes, or no?
If you want it, it's all yours.
I'll take it.
You froze up again.
Can you blame me? That was a dirty move.
Aw, cute.
This was how Serizawa began reading my novel.
Let's meet on the roof tomorrow for lunch.
Sure.
But what I didn't realize at the time...
Was that the popular Serizawa
acts weird around me!
Suzuki. Suzuki? Suzuki!
You'll be eating lunch with me from now on.
- Huh?
- We're learning to be friends!
Most tops are great cooks.
- Really?
- Leave this to me.
I'm going to be the King of Stewing!
I just don't know...